Arts and Sciences and Engineering Bulletins UP006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Announcement of Courses and Course Descriptions, 1943 -- 2012; UP006.003; 1.5 Linear Feet
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1987; UP006.003.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1988; UP006.003.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1988; UP006.003.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1989; UP006.003.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1989; UP006.003.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1990; UP006.003.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1990; UP006.003.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1991; UP006.003.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1991; UP006.003.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1992; UP006.003.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1992; UP006.003.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1993; UP006.003.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1993; UP006.003.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1994; UP006.003.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1994; UP006.003.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1995; UP006.003.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1995; UP006.003.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1996; UP006.003.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Course Descriptions, 2003 -- 2004; UP006.003.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Fall Course Schedule & Course Description, 2008; UP006.003.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Fall Course Schedule & Course Description, 2009; UP006.003.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Fall Course Schedule, 2010; UP006.003.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Spring Course Schedule, 2011; UP006.003.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Course Offerings & Course Descriptions, Fall, 2011; UP006.003.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Course Offerings & Course Descriptions, Spring, 2012; UP006.003.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Course Offerings & Course Descriptions, Fall, 2012; UP006.003.003.00027 (Box 3)
- Summer Session Bulletins, 1942 -- 2009; UP006.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Annual bulletin of information for summer school. Includes school description, course descriptions, roster of faculty.
  - Bulletin of Tufts College Summer Session, 1942; UP006.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer Term, 1945; UP006.004.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1946; UP006.004.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1947; UP006.004.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1948; UP006.004.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1949; UP006.004.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1950; UP006.004.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1951; UP006.004.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Tufts College Summer School, 1952; UP006.004.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College Summer School, 1953; UP006.004.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College Summer School, 1954; UP006.004.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College Summer School, 1955; UP006.004.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1956; UP006.004.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1957; UP006.004.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1958; UP006.004.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1959; UP006.004.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1960; UP006.004.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1961; UP006.004.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1962; UP006.004.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1963; UP006.004.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1964; UP006.004.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1965; UP006.004.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1966; UP006.004.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1967; UP006.004.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1968; UP006.004.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1969; UP006.004.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1970; UP006.004.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1971; UP006.004.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1972; UP006.004.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1973; UP006.004.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1974; UP006.004.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1975; UP006.004.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Summer School, 1976; UP006.004.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1977; UP006.004.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1978; UP006.004.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1979; UP006.004.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1980; UP006.004.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1981; UP006.004.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1982; UP006.004.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1983; UP006.004.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1984; UP006.004.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1985; UP006.004.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1986; UP006.004.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1987; UP006.004.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1988; UP006.004.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Summer School, 1989; UP006.004.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1990; UP006.004.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1991; UP006.004.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1992; UP006.004.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1993; UP006.004.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1994; UP006.004.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer School, 1995; UP006.004.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 1996 -- 1997; UP006.004.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 1998; UP006.004.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 1999; UP006.004.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2000 -- 2001; UP006.004.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2002; UP006.004.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2003; UP006.004.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2004; UP006.004.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Summer: A Course for Everyone, 2005 -- 2006; UP006.004.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2007; UP006.004.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2008; UP006.004.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Bulletin Summer Session, 2009; UP006.004.005.00027 (Box 5)